{
    "subject": "resource/Acacio_Gabriel_Viegas",
    "predicate": "property/ethnicity",
    "object": "Goan",
    "human_readable": "Acacio Gabriel Viegas is of Goan ethnicity.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9694269895553589,
            "question": "What is Acacio Gabriel Viegas's ethnicity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9518555998802185,
            "question": "Where does the ethnicity of Acacio Gabriel Viegas originate from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5040045976638794,
            "question": "Are there any famous people of Goan ethnicity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13916216790676117,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Goan culture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12255417555570602,
            "question": "How has Goan culture influenced other parts of the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.025296369567513466,
            "question": "Where is Goa located geographically?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.02436181530356407,
            "question": "What are some popular dishes from Goan cuisine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.020748388022184372,
            "question": "What is the history of Goa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.020645448938012123,
            "question": "What are some traditional customs or beliefs associated with Goa?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.01599038578569889,
            "question": "Is there a specific language spoken in Goa?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Acacio Gabriel Viegas is of Goan ethnicity.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3545_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some traditional customs or beliefs associated with Goa?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3545_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the history of Goa?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3545_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular dishes from Goan cuisine?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3545_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3545_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3545_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3545_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3545_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3545_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3545_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3545_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3545_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3545_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3545_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format containing the answer:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Acacio Gabriel Viegas was born in Arpora, Goa, which suggests that he has a connection to the region. Additionally, his election to the Bombay Municipal Corporation as the first Goan to be so elected (according to J Clement Vaz's book) and being credited with the discovery of the outbreak of bubonic plague in Bombay, India in 1896, further implies that he is of Goan ethnicity."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Dr. Acacio Gabriel Viegas was born in Arpora, Goa, and had a significant career in Bombay (which was then part of British India but had strong connections to Goa). This information supports the inference that he is of Goan ethnicity."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}